(Sheldon:)Are you monitoring
your circadian rhythms
(Sheldon:)in order to identify your periods
of maximum mental acuity?
(Sheldon:)I did that one summer.
(Sheldon:)Ah, youth.
(Amy:)No, I experienced some
distressing symptoms last night,
(Amy:)so I'm checking
my vital signs every hour.
(Sheldon:)I'd be happy to create a chart
(Sheldon:)and participate in a
differential diagnosis.
(Amy:)Oh, that sounds like fun.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)What were the symptoms?
(Amy:)Elevated heart rate,
moist palms, dry mouth
(Amy:)and localized
vascular throbbing.
(Sheldon:)Localized to what region?
(Amy:)Ears and genitalia.
(Amy:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)Not body parts
that usually team up.
(Sheldon:)What about
environmental factors?
(Sheldon:)Describe the scene for me.
(Amy:)I was sitting in a restaurant
with Penny and Bernadette,
(Amy:)drinking water-- carbonated
as it was a special occasion.